So, you know in horror movies when the girl's like,
"Oh, my god. There's something in the basement.
Let me just run down there in my underwear
and see what's going on, in the dark."
And you're like, "What is your problem?! Call the police!"
And she's like, "Okay," But it's too late,
Because she's already getting murdered.
Well, uh... my story's kind of like that.
It's a surprise for Spencer.
I'm just gonna walk in, and I'm gonna drop my coat on the ground.
He says he has this fantasy
that I'm a stripper with a heart of gold
and he's helping me put myself through college.
He didn't say the college part, did he?
Um, no. I-I wanted to create a 3-dimensional sex character.
Really? What's your stripper name?
Uh... Rebecca Johnson.
Your stripper name's Rebecca Johnson?
Boobies Johnson. T-two boobs Johnson.
Look at you, in the back of a cab, totally naked.